

Personal Info

Address

1-54-6 Minamisenju Arakawaku Tokyo Japan

Phone

+81 70 44 15 49 56

E-mail

hiroko.bouzas@gmail.com

Portfolio

http://hiroko.design

Working Condition

Eligible to work within EU

Language

Japanese

Native

English

Advanced

French

• • • • • • Conversation

Skills

Adobe Creative Suite



Prototyping tools (Sketch,

XD)



HTML, CSS



JavaScript



SEO Measurement



Hiroko Bouzas

UX/UI Designer, Graphic Designer

UX/UI design, graphic design professional with +10 years of experience over Japan, Australia and France. Various Work experiences, such as full stack designer in IT startups to lead UX designer in a big company, also wide experience as freelance designer/ web developer.

I enjoy working on challenging projects.

Experience

Always

Freelance Graphic, UX/UI Designer, Web Developer Anywhere in the world

- · Design consultation, branding for small businesses, startups.
- · Project management, scheduling, budget adjustment.
- UX/UI design for websites, native applications, Graphic design, Illustration.
- · Web programing, server setup.

2018 - now Art Director, Lead UX Designer

U-NEXT.Co.,Ltd. / Tokyo Japan

- Have been working on rebranding project with brand designers.
- Collaborating with stake holders to make the new brand identity that satisfies the aimed brand image.
- · Defining new customer journey with new brand identity.
- Implementing new brand identity to the product that has multiple platforms such as iOS, Android, Android TV, web, PlayStation.

2015 - 2018 Chief Designer (UX/UI Designer)

Zweispace Japan / Tokyo Japan

- Responsible for all the design materials of the company, supervised design consistency across products.
- Comprehensive design work from defining user stories to final products, considering usability and development efficiency.
- Front-end web development.
- Managing SEO for web based products, web advertisement such as Google AdWords, Facebook Ads, affiliate marketing.

2013 - 2014 Graphic Designer, UI Designer

Studio SPEC / Sydney Australia

- DTP design to transform complex information in simple way.
- · Teaching small class of graphic design foundation course.
- · UI design for website, web application.

2008 - 2012 Graphic Designer

UCHINO life style designing / Tokyo Japan

- Delivering graphic design, product design, package design for big named brands.
- · Learned principal idea of working as a team.

Education

2013-05 First Certificate in English (FCE)

Cambridge Examination / Sydney Australia

2004-04 to Bachelor of Arts / Visual Communication Design

2008-03 Musashino Art University/ Tokyo Japan